

MKRTICH ALEKSANYAN

UI Developer

About Me

I graduated from Yerevan State University faculty of physics. After university I started to undertake a web developer training at gConverter and I learned programming languages and improved my skills in different programming companies.

I've started to work since 2016.



+374 77 727246



amv.mkrtich@gmail.com



Armenia, Gyumri

LANGUAGE

- English pre intermediate
- Armenian native
- Russian proficient

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- SASS/SCSS
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Ract JS
- BEM
- Bootstrap
- Foundation
- SVG
- Adobe Photoshop / Figma / Zeplin
- Wordpress
- PHP
- MySQL

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer NODA Digital Agency - Australia Apr 2016 - Jul 2023

Wordpress Developer gVectors - Armenia Oct 2016 - Aug 2022

Web Developer gConverter - Armenia Mar 2016 - May 2021

Web development Trainer TCO - Software Development - Armenia Mar 2016 - May 2021

Web Developer SIclinic - Russia Apr 2017 - Jun 2020

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree Learning Sciences (2007 - 2011) Yerevan State University

Web development trainings gConverter - Armenia (Augost 2015 - March 2016)

PART OF PROJECTS

https://petsy.com.au/ https://oldquartercoffee.com.au/ https://spacenow.com/ https://www.mortels.com.au/ https://podshare.com.au/ https://www.endurobuilders.com.au/ https://www.digitalspotlight.com/

https://digitalspotlightfinance.com/

http://www.newtel.com.au/